<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="5" CreationDate="2015-07-14T18:39:27.757" Score="4" ViewCount="123" Body="&lt;p&gt;The proposal for this site only mentions &quot;Arabic.&quot; Which Arabic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a common type of Arabic called &quot;classical Arabic&quot; (fusha) which stretches back at least 1000 years back. It's still used today for most media (eg. newspapers, textbooks) and in universities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond this, each country has its own dialect (or slang) version of Arabic. This includes both use of vocabulary, and also actual grammar (or ignoring the classical grammar).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While some of the sample questions on Area 51 talk about Arabic in a specific area, the question is really how we should plan and organize questions, or whether we should focus exclusively on classical Arabic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="20" LastEditorUserId="20" LastEditDate="2015-07-14T22:27:41.087" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T16:43:23.787" Title="Which Arabic are we talking about?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="4"/>
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T18:42:42.553" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;While allowing non-classical Arabic questions will give us more questions being asked, I think it will hurt the site because of two reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Readability:&lt;/strong&gt; If users can ask questions in Arabic, you now need a bigger user base that covers whatever country-specific version the question is in.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answerability:&lt;/strong&gt; Like above, if we don't have site users who know that specific version of Arabic (and in sufficient depth and detail to give a strong answer), we'll end up with a bunch of open, unanswerable questions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, we can let this play out (allowing country-specific Arabic questions) and see what happens. As a start, we should at least try to &lt;em&gt;tag country-specific Arabic questions appropriately.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="20" LastActivityDate="2015-07-14T18:42:42.553" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T19:16:18.303" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;For both of the main potential audiences of this site, I think we should include the regional dialects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For native speakers, the regional dialects form a large portion of Arabic as it's spoken today.  For learners, learning at least one dialect is often considered a necessary part of learning the Arabic language (and is pretty important if you actually want to visit a country).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This does mean we should be careful with tagging questions, and it also means we should be open to questions having multiple answers corresponding to different regions.  But the StackExchange format is well-suited to that, and other sites handle the same issue fine.  (For instance, on Academia, many questions have multiple answers with begin by explaining which fields the answer is relevant to.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One final point: fusha refers to both Classical Arabic and Modern Standard Arabic.  These languages are pretty similar, but there are some usage differences.  So whether or not we include the regional dialects, we should keep in mind that some questions may have multiple answers depending on the language variant (and tag accordingly).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="5" LastActivityDate="2015-07-14T19:16:18.303" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T20:05:50.737" Score="-3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Arabic was never a single language, even before Islam and even when Islam came. That's why Quran was sent to Mohammed in 7 different tongues (dialects), not be confused with Qira'at (القراءات). The common dialect at that time was لغة قريش. It is called Arabic mainly because of the race, not because of the language itself. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyway, same thing is applicable now, the classical Arabic we see now is mainly from Quran and Current Quran is mainly from the Quraish version (one of the seven dialects). In addition to that, each country/region/tribe of Arabs has its own dialect/accent, nothing new here as this was the case throughout history. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To answer your question, this site should be about all Arabic Language variants (classic or dialects) especially that almost all Arabs are capable of understanding each other mutually with no problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastActivityDate="2015-07-14T20:05:50.737" CommentCount="4"/>
  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T20:06:44.950" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;As I see it, this issue can be broken into two distinct concerns:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Should we as a site cater to questions &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; dialectual variants of Arabic?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Should we as a site encourage posts &lt;em&gt;written&lt;/em&gt; in dialectual variants of Arabic?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first case, I think questions &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; different dialects should be allowed, for much the same reason Henry mentioned: &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/a/3/10&quot;&gt;The regional dialects form a large portion of Arabic as it's spoken today&lt;/a&gt;. Cutting dialects out of the scope would likely cut out a significant majority of our potential activity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the second case, however, I feel that there's value in establishing some clear guidelines to prevent the site from just becoming a mish-mash of dialects. I would suggest the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider English and Fusha as the &quot;official&quot; languages of this site&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Assuming that the majority of our users can (a) understand Fusha, and (b) understand English, seems to be a reasonable compromise (short of just abandoning English-language entirely, which given most of the posts on the site so far (including this meta) are written in English is probably going to be a hard sell)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Using regional dialects in meta discussions should be expressly discouraged; community opinion can only truly be gauged if the bulk of the community can reasonably &lt;em&gt;understand&lt;/em&gt; what is being discussed, and many Arabic dialects are not mutually understandable. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Meta posts, policy discussions, FAQs with any sort of &quot;official&quot; weight &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; be written in one or the other (ideally both).&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any meta posts which the Stack Exchange community team (rather than just the site community/moderators) may need to be aware of must be written in English, as few if any of them are fluent in Arabic. In particular, this would include things like bug reports and feature requests.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Allow questions on the main page in regional dialects, but only if they're expressly &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; some aspect of that dialect, and &lt;em&gt;tagged appropriately&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users should be allowed to ask questions in the manner which is most comfortable to them when possible; using their own dialect seems safe, so long as any possible answer would be relevant to that dialect&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It is reasonable to assume that any experts capable of answering a question &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; a particular dialect is also &lt;em&gt;fluent&lt;/em&gt; in that particular dialect. Conversely, it is reasonable to assume that any experts &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; fluent in that particular dialect are poorly qualified to answer questions &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; that particular dialect.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This allows users fluent/not-fluent in particular dialects to selectively ignore/highlight/select questions that they can actually understand based on tags.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Insist that answers on the main page only use dialect if the question is written in that dialect.&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;English questions should get English answers, and Arabic questions should get Arabic answers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Even if a question is tagged with a dialect, if it's asked in (a) Fusha, or (b) English, so must the answer be written&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, the only time a dialect should be used is if it&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;hellip;is a question about and tagged with that particular dialect, or&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;hellip;is an answer posted to a question using that dialect.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, either Fusha or English should be used.  From my understanding (I am hardly an Arabic native) Fusha is rather universally &lt;em&gt;understood&lt;/em&gt; among Arabic speakers, even when it's rarely if ever actually &lt;em&gt;spoken&lt;/em&gt;. So establishing it as the &lt;em&gt;lingua franca&lt;/em&gt; of Arabic here makes sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastEditorUserId="10" LastEditDate="2015-07-15T16:43:23.787" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T16:43:23.787" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T20:27:38.187" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;As discussed in the proposal, which I think we should stick to, this site is for any and all Arabic, including it's dialects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many users of the proposal signed up specifically for the questions about the dialects of the language as such we need to come up with a plan to support this otherwise we will drive people away.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As such this is not a question of &quot;if&quot; but &quot;how&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the proposal we hinted that classical (Fusha) Arabic was the default dialect of all questions/answers and I see no reason to change that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the big question, of which some of these answers try to solve, is how to deal with dialects when they do arise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Having read @GoldPseudo's answer it seems he knows what he is on about and his ideas seem sound. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It makes sense that if someone asks in English it is likely that they are a student or learner of Arabic, as such the answers should probably be English as well. Likewise, if the question is in Arabic there is no use writing in a totally different language (English) since that person is speaking Arabic, and this is Arabic SE after-all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We should probably encourage this stance and punish those who do not follow it with downvotes to try and create some norm, else I can see this quickly becoming a mess.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We should also allocate tags for dialects as suggested. We need to be more careful about this last point though and I am still unclear exactly how we should structure this. It might come down to just seeing what actual users do and then cleaning their process up into something workable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56" LastActivityDate="2015-07-14T20:27:38.187" CommentCount="3"/>
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T21:54:34.180" Score="4" ViewCount="85" Body="&lt;p&gt;I noticed that first questions have many mistakes: Some don't use transliteration at all, some uses Arabizi. Both cases make questions and answers not readable by a non-native speaker of Arabic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I propose to choose one or two unified transliteration to use through all the site questions and answers. I suggest:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/ISO_233&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ISO 233&lt;/a&gt; : &lt;code&gt;الله&lt;/code&gt; ==&gt; &lt;code&gt;ʾllh&lt;/code&gt; (international standard)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Buckwalter_transliteration&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Buckwalter&lt;/a&gt;:  &lt;code&gt;الله&lt;/code&gt; ==&gt; &lt;code&gt;Allh&lt;/code&gt; (used broadly by linguists and computer scientists)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am against using &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arabic_chat_alphabet&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Arabizi&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please, suggest any other useful alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also I suggest to attach any transliteration with its Arabic word like &lt;code&gt;qwl قول (saying)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T15:50:12.163" Title="Shouldn't we discuss using transliterations?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T22:02:58.073" Score="6" ViewCount="105" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/9/%D9%85%D8%A7-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%81%D8%B1%D9%82-%D8%A8%D9%8A%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%82%D9%85%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D9%88-%D8%A7%D9%84-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B4%D9%85%D8%B3%D9%8A%D8%A9&quot;&gt;ما الفرق بين &lt;code&gt;ال&lt;/code&gt; القمرية و &lt;code&gt;ال&lt;/code&gt; الشمسية ؟&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both the question and the answer are in Arabic, non-Arabic speakers will have almost zero chance in understanding the question or the answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I highly doubt that is goal of SE Arabic&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="63" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T02:45:47.897" Title="Are we discussing Arabic language in Arabic or are we discussing Arabic language in English?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7" CreationDate="2015-07-14T22:28:24.197" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.islam.stackexchange.com/a/9/22&quot;&gt;The recommendation I made for Islam.SE&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I would propose basing our system on the one that's been developed for Wikipedia &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Manual_of_Style/Arabic&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Standard Transliteration&lt;/strong&gt; rules (e.g., &lt;em&gt;arkan&lt;/em&gt; instead of either &lt;em&gt;arkān&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;arkaan&lt;/em&gt;) should be sufficient for most purposes. If an exact reading is required for something it would probably be better to just quote the Arabic text itself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Strict (rather than Standard) transliteration would be even better, since it clearly and reversibly maps to the Arabic alphabet, but I feel enforcing it too strictly would be difficult because of the difficulty in typing the necessary diacritics on a standard keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can understand the appeal for Buckwalter from a linguistic point of view &amp;mdash; not only does it clearly and reversibly map to the Arabic alphabet, but it does so with standard characters &amp;mdash; but it also has the annoying side-effect of being difficult to actually just &lt;em&gt;read&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And yes, I too strongly oppose any suggestion to use Arabizi. It just looks...ugly. And unprofessional. But mostly ugly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2015-07-14T22:28:24.197" CommentCount="4"/>
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T22:32:16.373" Score="3" ViewCount="48" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've stumbled upon following &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/q/23/7&quot;&gt;question&lt;/a&gt; with the title 'Which words are the same across Hebrew and Arabic?'&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've answered it in some short sentences, referring to semitic languages. Still I feel this question should be closed. Are questions like that conform to the community guidelines (or to the one we want to establish)?&#xA;What are the reasons to close questions like that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An obvious reason to close the question would be that it is too broad, a short answer actually answering the question can't be provided. Leaving that aside, questions like that would give this site character of an etymological dictionary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="7" LastActivityDate="2015-07-16T21:10:38.543" Title="Community guideline concerning closing of question" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;questions&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="11" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10" CreationDate="2015-07-14T22:41:49.723" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's simply too broad. What do you think they would do in SE EL if someone posted a question like &quot;Which words are the same across English and German?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="63" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2015-07-15T05:24:04.940" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T05:24:04.940" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="12" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-14T23:00:56.180" Score="1" ViewCount="57" Body="&lt;p&gt;The link below shows no users&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users?tab=moderators&quot;&gt;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users?tab=moderators&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="63" LastActivityDate="2015-07-14T23:11:21.900" Title="Aren't there any moderators in SE Arabic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="12" CreationDate="2015-07-14T23:05:05.800" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, beta sites are moderated by the &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/about/team&quot;&gt;Stack Exchange community team&lt;/a&gt;. Once we've started to establish a community and they have enough information to gauge who will (and will not) be a good moderator, they'll appoint site-specific moderators. This should take place in a couple weeks (about a week into public beta), but may take more or less time depending on how well (and how quickly) the community &lt;em&gt;gels&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They do take community input into consideration, so starting a thread discussing who would make a good moderator would be a valuable asset for the community team when they do appoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Relevant blog post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.stackexchange.com/2010/07/moderator-pro-tempore/&quot;&gt;https://blog.stackexchange.com/2010/07/moderator-pro-tempore/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastEditorUserId="10" LastEditDate="2015-07-14T23:11:21.900" LastActivityDate="2015-07-14T23:11:21.900" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="14" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10" CreationDate="2015-07-15T00:15:35.017" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have voted to close that question. I will use this post to try and explain my logic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have currently brought over the rules used on SO, known also as StackOverflow (where I am active).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These rules might not apply to this site but only time will tell so I will change how I use this site as situations force me to change how I think about this site's moderation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First off, I do still stand by my decision to state that your answer does not really answer the question and that the one below yours goes as close as possible, but that might be my own misconception of what defines an answer here. On SO your answer would have been deleted and converted into a comment and that might just be my misconception of applying SO rules here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now back to the topic: whether a question can be answered or not is not based on whether or not the answer is short. Take some of the best network questions, they can be pages long at times. A close reason is not &quot;the answer is not short enough&quot;, it is about whether or not the topic is too broad that even a long answer couldn't answer it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this case it would require literally a word by word comparison of both languages to complete the entire question, even though one answer goes some way. That is just an impossibly huge task for an answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As such this question is considered too broad in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T00:15:35.017" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="15" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2015-07-15T00:23:05.007" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;We did talk about this in Area51. The consensus there was that if native Arabic speakers want to answer only in Arabic on only Arabic questions then that is up to them. Not much we can do about it since this site is designed for everyone, not just those whose first language is English.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is said that if the question is in English then you should answer in English.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for understanding the questions: if you cannot yet piece together Arabic via your own understanding of it's structure and using Google translate to fill in the gaps of unknown words then the purely Arabic questions might be too high a level for you anyway; you might be tying to run before you can walk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was found that most who would ask/answer in Arabic would be scholars and advanced students, whereas those who are still not totally accustomed to speaking Arabic on a daily basis yet will easily feed on the newbie questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to say whether this will hold true yet, we need to get more questions and community but that was the assumption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a footnote: there was talk about allowing people to translate Arabic questions and answers to have a English definition side by side, but again, not sure about that currently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will just take it as it comes on this one, impossible to foresee how it will pan out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an edit: that does seem like a question whose answer should be in English and Arabic, especially since an English edition of the question was provided.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56" LastEditorUserId="56" LastEditDate="2015-07-15T00:30:21.077" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T00:30:21.077" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="16" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2015-07-15T02:45:47.897" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Based on the discussion in Area 51, I understood the goal of SE Arabic to be for all levels---the equivalent of both English Language &amp;amp; Usage and English Language Learners.  That could include both basic questions in English by people who wouldn't be able to translate an Arabic answer, and questions written in Arabic by native speakers which will likely be answered by other native speakers also in Arabic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a community, we need to start developing norms.  I would suggest:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users should be thoughtful about their choice of language.  Very basic questions are probably more useful when asked and answered in English.  More advanced questions more probably benefit from sticking to Arabic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Try to have answers in the same language as the question.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Take advantage of the community editing features of stack exchange: it's a service to the community when people translate a good question or answer into the other language so we have both alongside each other.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="5" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T02:45:47.897" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="17" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-15T03:07:10.233" Score="6" ViewCount="46" Body="&lt;p&gt;It has been brought up on the main Meta.SE &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/260709/please-enable-arabic-tags-for-arabic-se&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; so I am bringing it up here, I would like to ask if it is possible for arabic tagging support to be provided. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T16:20:11.363" Title="Can Arabic Tagging be supported/provided?" Tags="&lt;feature-request&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="18" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-15T03:58:17.897" Score="4" ViewCount="61" Body="&lt;p&gt;حاولت طرح سؤال قبل قليل لكن تعرضت لي رسالة خطأ تقول:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;This question body does not meet our quality standards. Please make&#xA;  sure that it completely describes your problem - including what you&#xA;  have already tried - and is written using proper grammar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/C27O5.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="95" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2015-07-15T17:49:23.143" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T17:49:23.143" Title="لماذا لا أقدر طرح سؤالي؟" Tags="&lt;bug&gt;&lt;status-completed&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="19" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="20" CreationDate="2015-07-15T15:15:10.953" Score="-1" ViewCount="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it suppose to show only the unanswered questions &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/unanswered&quot;&gt;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/unanswered&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="63" LastEditorUserId="45" LastEditDate="2015-07-15T16:20:37.590" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T16:20:37.590" Title="The unanswered tab shows questions with answers" Tags="&lt;bug&gt;&lt;status-bydesign&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="20" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="19" CreationDate="2015-07-15T15:40:13.560" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;That is by design. If the questioner hasn't considered any of the given answers worth &lt;em&gt;accepting&lt;/em&gt;, nor has the community considered any of them useful enough to even have a positive score, then the site considers it a question that still needs a proper answer: So far as that page is concerned, &quot;Unanswered&quot; means &quot;No upvoted or accepted answers&quot;, not &quot;No posted answers at all&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/bqUMm.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the &quot;Unanswered&quot; page, there's a &quot;No Answers&quot; tab that will display posts that explicitly have &lt;em&gt;no posted answers&lt;/em&gt;, if that's something you actually want.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See also:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/18870/132874&quot;&gt;Why does the &amp;quot;Unanswered Questions&amp;quot; tab show questions that have answers?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.stackexchange.com/2008/09/ok-now-define-answered/&quot;&gt;OK, Now Define &quot;Answered&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastEditorUserId="10" LastEditDate="2015-07-15T15:46:37.550" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T15:46:37.550" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="21" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="17" CreationDate="2015-07-15T16:20:11.363" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately not at this time, as Sammaye correctly mentioned in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Islam site uses Arabic words transliterated into Latin script in &lt;a href=&quot;http://islam.stackexchange.com/tags&quot;&gt;their tags&lt;/a&gt;, with the Arabic words written in the tag wikis and summaries. I think that's just about the best we've got as far as workarounds go for now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="45" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T16:20:11.363" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="22" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-15T21:50:12.823" Score="0" ViewCount="39" Body="&lt;p&gt;I asked &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/90/what-words-are-feminine-according-to-the-arabs?&quot;&gt;this question about listing words that are considered feminine by Arabs&lt;/a&gt;. It was closed as &quot;too broad&quot; with some comments relating to other, open-ended list-type questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My understanding is that of &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/90/what-words-are-feminine-according-to-the-arabs?noredirect=1#comment135_90&quot;&gt;this comment&lt;/a&gt;: this is not an open-ended nor large list of words. It's supposed to be a small (dozen or so), well-known, non-changing list.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The question already has two votes to re-open, so please consider casting yours too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This begs the deeper question of what, if any, &quot;list&quot;-type questions would make sense for the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="20" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T22:30:45.240" Title="What kind of word-list questions are acceptable?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="23" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22" CreationDate="2015-07-15T22:25:43.227" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think the key criterion for a word-list question is that it has to be feasible to list all the words. In practice this means that the list must be relatively small (certainly &amp;lt;100, perhaps smaller still), well-defined, and non-changing. (Otherwise an answer can never be complete or correct, as there will always be entries either missing or debatable).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As to the question that motivated this meta, the reference I have to hand (A Reference Grammar of MSA, K. Ryding, 2005) says &quot;This is a small, defined set&quot; - so I believe a good, definitive answer is possible (and would also be incredibly useful to learners).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="70" LastEditorUserId="70" LastEditDate="2015-07-15T22:30:45.240" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T22:30:45.240" CommentCount="3"/>
  <row Id="24" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="27" CreationDate="2015-07-16T07:52:40.910" Score="7" ViewCount="40" Body="&lt;p&gt;I noticed that many of the questions asked on the site uses the [question] tag, is that acceptable? I cannot see any value in this tag, aren't these all questions after all? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe this tag is used to overcome the tagging requirement without having to think of the proper tags, specially that there are not much of them yet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there a way to prohibit such tag, or should we manually re-tag these questions?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="118" LastActivityDate="2015-07-18T11:37:44.793" Title="Tagging questions with a [question] tag" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;retagging&gt;&lt;asking&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="25" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-16T10:27:40.917" Score="4" ViewCount="32" Body="&lt;p&gt;How should poetry verse-haves (Sadr and Ajuz - صدر وعجز بيت الشعر) be separated?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Posters uses various way to do so, for example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;قفا نبك من ذِكرى حبيب ومنزل | بسِقطِ اللِّوى بينَ الدَّخول فحَوْملِ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;قفا نبك من ذِكرى حبيب ومنزل ---- بسِقطِ اللِّوى بينَ الدَّخول فحَوْملِ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;قفا نبك من ذِكرى حبيب ومنزل *** بسِقطِ اللِّوى بينَ الدَّخول فحَوْملِ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;قفا نبك من ذِكرى حبيب ومنزل ... بسِقطِ اللِّوى بينَ الدَّخول فحَوْملِ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should we be concerned about this issue? Is there some form that might has advantage over others?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm concerned here about two issues here; clarity and searching.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="118" LastEditorUserId="42" LastEditDate="2015-07-21T02:52:10.920" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T02:52:10.920" Title="Poetry verse-halves separator" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;search&gt;&lt;formatting&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1"/>
  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-16T11:35:28.240" Score="6" ViewCount="119" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since you can ask in Arabic or English, it will happen to find duplicate between the two languages. Should we close them as duplicate?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From my point of view, we can't consider them like that: Many users know only English and Many know only Arabic. You can't just tell the OP, go and check the other question; He/She will not understand it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastEditorUserId="42" LastEditDate="2015-07-25T01:09:07.980" LastActivityDate="2015-07-25T01:09:07.980" Title="Arabic question is duplicate of an English one , should we close it as duplicate?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1"/>
  <row Id="27" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="24" CreationDate="2015-07-16T15:12:17.527" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Questions should absolutely not be tagged with &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/question&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;question&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;question&lt;/a&gt; unless they are specifically about how to form a question grammatically in Arabic. (I can't read Arabic, so I can't tell if that's the case with these questions.) The &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/question&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;question&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;question&lt;/a&gt; tag should be removed from those questions, and they should be given more useful tags. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.stackexchange.com/2010/08/the-death-of-meta-tags/&quot;&gt;This blog post&lt;/a&gt; is a good explanation of why we do not use meta-tags like &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/question&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;question&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;question&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="45" LastActivityDate="2015-07-16T15:12:17.527" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="28" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="26" CreationDate="2015-07-16T16:58:22.073" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would say no. Closing as Duplicate is basically just saying &quot;Every single possible answer to &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; question is a possible answer to &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; question&quot;, but under the general principle of &quot;English questions should have English answers and Arabic questions should have Arabic answers&quot;, that would not be the case: Like you say, &lt;em&gt;Arabic&lt;/em&gt; answers would not be of any use to someone asking an &lt;em&gt;English&lt;/em&gt; question, and vice-versa.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here, the only way I can see closing as Duplicate being appropriate is if the duplicate target is &lt;em&gt;bilingual&lt;/em&gt;, written in both Arabic &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; English (the question, as well as all answers). I couldn't say whether it's worth creating a &lt;em&gt;third&lt;/em&gt; (bilingual) question &amp;mdash; translating all the top answers from the originals &amp;mdash; just so you can close the other two as duplicates of it, but I imagine for some questions that would be a viable course of action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2015-07-16T16:58:22.073" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="30" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="33" CreationDate="2015-07-16T18:35:38.683" Score="4" ViewCount="43" Body="&lt;p&gt;I just came across the tag &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/genders&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;genders&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;genders&lt;/a&gt;. I wanted to change it to &quot;gender&quot;, but I was not able to and was asked to &quot;raise it [i.e. the issue] on meta&quot;. So this is what I am doing now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tag should be &lt;strong&gt;gender&lt;/strong&gt; and not &lt;strong&gt;genders&lt;/strong&gt; (i.e. should be without the &quot;s&quot;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="28" LastEditorUserId="28" LastEditDate="2015-07-17T02:49:11.597" LastActivityDate="2015-07-17T16:24:13.263" Title="Tag: genders -- change to: gender" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="31" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10" CreationDate="2015-07-16T21:10:38.543" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;You are totally correct. The &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/23/which-words-are-the-same-across-hebrew-and-arabic&quot;&gt;mentioned question&lt;/a&gt; has been put on hold as it's indeed too broad!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172" LastActivityDate="2015-07-16T21:10:38.543" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="32" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="26" CreationDate="2015-07-16T21:34:48.530" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/8/are-we-discussing-arabic-language-in-arabic-or-are-we-discussing-arabic-language/15#comment28_15&quot;&gt;In my opinion&lt;/a&gt;, and for indexing purposes, we should add the translation in the older question and answer, then mark the new question as duplicate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By this way, we can make sure that all users can find the correct answer in one indexed link, plus, all answers can be collected in one place! :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172" LastActivityDate="2015-07-16T21:34:48.530" CommentCount="5"/>
  <row Id="33" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="30" CreationDate="2015-07-17T10:45:44.277" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am in full agreement - when I asked &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/136/which-words-can-be-either-masculine-or-feminine&quot;&gt;my question&lt;/a&gt; I was surprised to be forced into &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/genders&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;genders&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;genders&lt;/a&gt; when &quot;gender&quot; seems much more appropriate. In general in English the singular &quot;gender&quot; is used to refer to the topic of grammatical gender in general, so that's what the tag name should be.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="70" LastActivityDate="2015-07-17T10:45:44.277" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="34" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="30" CreationDate="2015-07-17T16:24:13.263" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I agree, and I have made this change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="45" LastActivityDate="2015-07-17T16:24:13.263" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="35" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-18T08:34:48.307" Score="0" ViewCount="25" Body="&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to cast a vote for closing a question. The reason was that I thought the question was &lt;em&gt;too specified&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This reason, which I know from other SE sites, did not show up as an option. I think it should be added.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions may be too broad and unlikely to reeve a definite answer. Other questions however may be to narrow and will be of interest for only one or few people by not for the community of Arabic language learner sand enthusiasts. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="28" LastActivityDate="2015-07-20T20:22:02.140" Title="Reasons for vote-to-close" Tags="&lt;feature-request&gt;&lt;vote-to-close&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="36" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="24" CreationDate="2015-07-18T11:37:44.793" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is no &lt;em&gt;automatic&lt;/em&gt; way of prohibiting the existence of poor tags, or the practice of abusing existing tags. These moderation tasks have to be done by the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A basic moderation task is to make sure that new questions are tagged appropriately. This means adding missing tags and removing inappropriate tags, and possibly adding a comment pointing the user to the tag-wiki to explain proper use of a particular tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, there are currently a lot of tags with no wiki-text. As such, users have no guidance as to whether a tag is appropriate for their question. This leads to meta-tagging and other abuses. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Along with the lack of guidance, not requiring wiki-text when creating new tags leads to a proliferation of separate tags where tag-synonyms might be more appropriate (&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/article&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/arabic-the&quot;&gt;arabic-the&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/al&quot;&gt;al&lt;/a&gt;). There should be cases where one tag is used and another is not, whereas &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/arabic-the&quot;&gt;arabic-the&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/al&quot;&gt;al&lt;/a&gt; would always be together since they refer to the exact same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just as new questions are moderated, new tags should be moderated. Each tag should have a tag-wiki which justifies its existence and distinguishes its use from existing tags. If these requirements cannot be met, then the new tag should be removed from the list of available tags.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="170" LastActivityDate="2015-07-18T11:37:44.793" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="37" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-18T16:38:42.557" Score="3" ViewCount="63" Body="&lt;p&gt;incorrect assessing:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;This post appears to be a duplicate of هل هناك أسماء لا تتضمن التذكير&#xA;  أو التأنيث؟&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/S1a0j.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="95" LastActivityDate="2015-07-22T10:15:46.977" Title="question is not duplicate" Tags="&lt;bug&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="6"/>
  <row Id="38" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-18T18:04:46.003" Score="-2" ViewCount="48" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/a/54/70&quot;&gt;My answer&lt;/a&gt; to the question about silent letters in Arabic has so far received three downvotes (as well as one upvote).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ordinarily with a downvote I don't understand I'd shrug and say &quot;downvotes happen&quot;, but three on the same question - and with only one upvote - make me think there must be something seriously wrong with the answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the only &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/39/are-there-any-silent-letters-in-arabic/54#comment204_54&quot;&gt;comments&lt;/a&gt; left on the answer complain that the word &quot;مائة&quot; was misspelt. Once I added references to show that this &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a valid spelling, the commenter &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/39/are-there-any-silent-letters-in-arabic/54#comment217_54&quot;&gt;appeared to be satisfied&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I'm at a loss to understand what is wrong here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Does the answer not address the question? (I believe it does since it contains words in which not all the letters are pronounced.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is there some error in what the answer claims? (I've added references to back up what I say.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is it defective in some other way?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And, in general, how should the answer be improved?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I feel this is something we need to be clear about as a community, because I believe that my answer is a good one, though clearly others disagree - and if there is a lot of disagreement in the community over what makes a good answer, we won't get a lot of good answers and people will leave...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="70" LastEditorUserId="70" LastEditDate="2015-07-20T21:11:27.597" LastActivityDate="2015-07-20T21:11:27.597" Title="Downvotes to answer on &quot;silent letters&quot; question" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;down-votes&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="39" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="38" CreationDate="2015-07-18T19:05:26.437" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, I didn't really get satisfied but, I came to know that this exact word is a bit controversial.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The question is clear. despite those facts, and even if we consider your word is correct in spelling, it doesn't really provide an answer!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is anyways only a word, not a grammar rule. I can give you tens of similar words where a letter isn't pronounced in those particular words!&#xA;&lt;br&gt;However, we can't consider them as a rule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172" LastActivityDate="2015-07-18T19:05:26.437" CommentCount="6"/>
  <row Id="40" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-20T06:56:05.327" Score="4" ViewCount="145" Body="&lt;p&gt;I find myself having to zoom in to read what is written at times, especially when vowel signs are present.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does anyone have any prior experience with this kind of an issue (I'm thinking maybe from islam.stackexchange.com)? Are there any workarounds for making the typeface larger without having to resort to zooming in and out?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a few of my questions in which I cite Qur'anic verses I find it much easier to just link an image of the verse rather than mention the text itself, but this won't always be possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="29" LastEditorUserId="45" LastEditDate="2015-07-20T20:52:01.033" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T17:38:56.383" Title="Arabic script is hard to read" Tags="&lt;bug&gt;&lt;typeface&gt;&lt;design&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="41" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="35" CreationDate="2015-07-20T20:22:02.140" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;As goldPseudo noted &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/35/reasons-for-vote-to-close#comment33_35&quot;&gt;in the comments above&lt;/a&gt;, Too Localized was removed as a close reason &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/184154/165581&quot;&gt;back in 2013&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Too Localized was, by far, the most misused close reason in our surveys, with both Community Managers and Moderators deeming over 50% of randomly sampled TL closures to not have merited closure (including on SO).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Today, TL &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; used helpfully on code dump questions on SO, but the new OT reasons are where this is now correctly addressed. SO can use &quot;Large blocks of code with requests for debugging without meaningful supporting info&quot; as a specific OT reason.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So what does this mean for Arabic? Well, with enough consensus, the community could add a custom off-topic close reason for cases like these. But in the meantime it's important to think through why a &quot;too localized&quot; question is actually bad for Arabic Language SE. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One result of &quot;too localized&quot; being removed as a network-wide close reason is that communities are now better able to decide for themselves that constitutes a useful question. On a language site like Arabic, many questions would qualify as what used to be &quot;too localized&quot; on Stack Overflow. They answer one person's question, but they don't always solve a common problem people have when writing or speaking Arabic that they'll end up searching for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And yet, &lt;strong&gt;we still find such questions (examples: &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/q/43/45&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/q/47/45&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;) valuable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; as we build a compendium of knowledge about Arabic--and a community of knowledgeable people who like learning and teaching about Arabic concepts and history.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, tl;dr: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;Too Localized&quot; was removed as a close reason deliberately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If this community finds questions like those to be counterproductive or bad for the site, they can still be closed with custom reasons.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;But I'm not as sure as you are that they should be closed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1: I can't read Arabic so I've done my best to choose questions that I think illustrate my point, but please let me know if I'm off base here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="45" LastActivityDate="2015-07-20T20:22:02.140" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="42" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="40" CreationDate="2015-07-20T20:44:02.617" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes, the font is terrible (on my computer, at least - people may have different experiences on different web browsers/OSs/form factors etc).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm not aware of a good workaround, other than zooming in - you could potentially do something with a &lt;a href=&quot;http://webdesign.about.com/od/userstylesheets/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;user stylesheet&lt;/a&gt; or a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greasemonkey&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Greasemonkey&lt;/a&gt; script to change the font, but that seems like a lot of work!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm hoping the Stack Exchange team update the style at some point to make Arabic text more readable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="70" LastActivityDate="2015-07-20T20:44:02.617" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="43" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="40" CreationDate="2015-07-20T22:07:10.993" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Here's a greasemonkey script (Slightly modified from original source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/learn_arabic/comments/2zpobd/arabic_font_size/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/learn_arabic/comments/2zpobd/arabic_font_size/&lt;/a&gt;) which will detect Arabic text on any *.stackexchange.com site (including chat) and increase the size (without affecting non-Arabic text):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;// ==UserScript==&#xA;// @name        Arabic font size fixer&#xA;// @include     http://*.stackexchange.com/*&#xA;// @description Increases the font size of Arabic text&#xA;// @grant       GM_addStyle&#xA;// ==/UserScript==&#xA;&#xA;// adjust for flavor&#xA;GM_addStyle(&quot;span[lang~='ar'] {font-size: 130% !important }&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;// code by James Padolsey;&#xA;// http://james.padolsey.com/javascript/find-and-replace-text-with-javascript/&#xA;function findAndReplace(searchText, replacement, searchNode) {&#xA;    if (!searchText || typeof replacement === 'undefined') {&#xA;        // Throw error here if you want...&#xA;        return;&#xA;    }&#xA;    var regex = typeof searchText === 'string' ?&#xA;                new RegExp(searchText, 'g') : searchText,&#xA;        childNodes = (searchNode || document.body).childNodes,&#xA;        cnLength = childNodes.length,&#xA;        excludes = 'html';&#xA;    while (cnLength--) {&#xA;        var currentNode = childNodes[cnLength];&#xA;        if (currentNode.nodeType === 1 &amp;amp;&amp;amp;&#xA;            (excludes + ',').indexOf(currentNode.nodeName.toLowerCase() + ',') === -1) {&#xA;            arguments.callee(searchText, replacement, currentNode);&#xA;        }&#xA;        if (currentNode.nodeType !== 3 || !regex.test(currentNode.data) ) {&#xA;            continue;&#xA;        }&#xA;        var parent = currentNode.parentNode,&#xA;            frag = (function(){&#xA;                var html = currentNode.data.replace(regex, replacement),&#xA;                    wrap = document.createElement('div'),&#xA;                    frag = document.createDocumentFragment();&#xA;                wrap.innerHTML = html;&#xA;                while (wrap.firstChild) {&#xA;                    frag.appendChild(wrap.firstChild);&#xA;                }&#xA;                return frag;&#xA;            })();&#xA;        parent.insertBefore(frag, currentNode);&#xA;        parent.removeChild(currentNode);&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;findAndReplace('([\u0600-\u06FF]+( [\u0600-\u06FF]+)*)', '&amp;lt;span lang=&quot;ar&quot;&amp;gt;$1&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;')&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adjusting the &lt;code&gt;GM_addStyle(...);&lt;/code&gt; line lets you tweak things to your liking; as is, this will increase the font size by 30% but otherwise stick to the defaults, but with a little knowledge of CSS it's easy to change the size, color, and even the actual font:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No extension&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/bfB6r.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;GM_addStyle(&quot;span[lang~='ar'] {font-size: 130% !important }&quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/KbXSc.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;GM_addStyle(&quot;span[lang~='ar'] {font-family: andalus; color: green !important }&quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/lpLU6.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;GM_addStyle(&quot;span[lang~='ar'] {font-family: arabic typesetting; font-size: 200% !important }&quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/CY7xf.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastEditorUserId="10" LastEditDate="2015-07-21T17:38:56.383" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T17:38:56.383" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="44" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-21T02:29:48.703" Score="2" ViewCount="77" Body="&lt;p&gt;Arabic texts are aligned to left. For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;عنوان:&lt;/strong&gt; هذا نص عربي.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When a question/answer is all in Arabic, the text preferably be aligned to right. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Numbers in list start from left , while the Arabic start from right:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;تعريف&lt;/strong&gt;: كلمة عربية&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Parenthesis/Quotes/Symbols does not respect Right-to-left when ending with them in Arabic texts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;كلمة عربية (شرح). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;كلمة عربية &quot;شرح&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T16:13:19.237" Title="Align / RTL / Bidi problems for Arabic texts" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;bug&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="45" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25" CreationDate="2015-07-21T02:51:30.517" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't see a problem using any separator. I have the idea of applying  a feature request , a feature of Auto-highlighting of Arabic poetry. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Something like this&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;[arabic-poetry]&#xA;[separator &quot;.&quot;]&#xA;قفا نبك من ذِكرى حبيب ومنزل&#xA;بسِقطِ اللِّوى بينَ الدَّخول فحَوْملِ&#xA;فتوضح فالمقراة لم يَعفُ رسمهاَ&#xA;لما نسجتْها من جَنُوب وشمالِ&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;to get somethings&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;قفا نبك من ذِكرى حبيب ومنزل............بسِقطِ اللِّوى بينَ الدَّخول فحَوْملِ&#xA;فتوضح فالمقراة لم يَعفُ رسمهاَ...............لما نسجتْها من جَنُوب وشمالِ&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;                       قفا نبك من ذِكرى حبيب ومنزل&#xA;بسِقطِ اللِّوى بينَ الدَّخول فحَوْملِ&#xA;                        فتوضح فالمقراة لم يَعفُ رسمهاَ&#xA;لما نسجتْها من جَنُوب وشمالِ&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Centering and Justifying the text and adding the separator between each couple of lines. And preferably giving it a nice font and nice style. highlighting vowels as an extra.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T02:51:30.517" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="46" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44" CreationDate="2015-07-21T09:45:37.520" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes, this had been annoying me, too :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't know of a workaround for the first two issues - I think the SE folks need to add support for the &lt;code&gt;dir=&quot;rtl&quot;&lt;/code&gt; attribute on a number of tags - at the very least &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. Or perhaps start using &lt;code&gt;dir=&quot;auto&quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The third issue (parentheses/quotes/etc), at least, can be worked around by adding a Unicode &quot;right-to-left marker&quot; character at the end of the text (after the &quot;broken&quot; punctuation). This can either be an explicit character (U+200F), or the corresponding HTML entity &lt;code&gt;&amp;amp;#x200f;&lt;/code&gt; (or &lt;code&gt;&amp;amp;rlm;&lt;/code&gt;). For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original (broken)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;كلمة عربية (شرح).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Using a literal RLM character after the &quot;.&quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;كلمة عربية (شرح).‏&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Using an HTML entity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;كلمة عربية (شرح).&amp;rlm;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adding the HTML entity is easy (you can just type &lt;code&gt;&amp;amp;rlm;&lt;/code&gt; into the edit window), but the trouble is that, although the final (rendered) text looks good, the text in the edit box is still all in the wrong order (and looks worse because now you have the extra &lt;code&gt;&amp;amp;rlm;&lt;/code&gt; cluttering things up).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adding the literal character is trickier, but it makes the edited text look good too. One option, on Windows, is to use Notepad, and choose &quot;Insert Unicode Control Character -&gt; RLM&quot; from the menu - then copy and paste into the edit window.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="70" LastEditorUserId="70" LastEditDate="2015-07-21T16:13:19.237" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T16:13:19.237" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="47" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7" CreationDate="2015-07-21T15:50:12.163" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Writing in the Arabic script requires some knowledge of the script, some knowledge of computing in Arabic, and possibly some limitations associated with the user's computer. We don't know why a user chose to use transliteration, so I suggest that we allow people to ask and answer questions using whatever script/scheme allows them to communicate (even Arabizi).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each transliteration scheme is intended for a specific purpose. A priori, we do not know the reason a user is using a particular transliteration scheme, and if we were to enforce a particular transliteration scheme, then we might be excluding users from the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the transliteration scheme used by a user is not sufficiently clear to other users, then we can always put the question on hold as &quot;Unclear due to ambiguous transliteration.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, reviewers can easily add the proper Arabic script next to the transliterations in questions and accepted answers. It would be best if the users themselves could use the Arabic script for words and the International Phonetic Alphabet (IPA) for pronunciations, but do we want to exclude users if they can't?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="170" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T15:50:12.163" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="48" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="26" CreationDate="2015-07-22T07:36:56.473" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;When a question is marked as duplicate, does it prevent new answers? Does it get deleted? These would be additional reasons to not mark these questions as duplicates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would prefer to leave these pairs of questions open for the reasons @bigOTHER gave in the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Translation is difficult for reviewers, but allowing users to answer the duplicate question effectively gets the translation done, and rewards the translators with reputation, which they deserve for their contribution to the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the sidebar there is a list of &lt;code&gt;Linked&lt;/code&gt; questions, so it makes sense that equivalent questions in the two languages are at least linked, if not marked duplicate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="170" LastActivityDate="2015-07-22T07:36:56.473" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="49" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37" CreationDate="2015-07-22T10:15:46.977" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've had a look at this and run the provided text through the engine a few times, and ultimately it comes down to an inherent problem in telling the difference between two posts with &lt;em&gt;very short body text&lt;/em&gt; (not the title - the actual body). I can investigate this, but I suspect the &lt;em&gt;ideal&lt;/em&gt; solution is simply: &lt;em&gt;have longer question text&lt;/em&gt;. It seems unlikely that the full nuance and depth of most questions can be conveyed in 30 characters - indeed, it is usually a warning sign if the question title and question body are virtually the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However! I don't understand the question or the nuance (due to the language barrier); so allow me to ask: &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; both the questions (the body, not the title), &lt;em&gt;as asked&lt;/em&gt;, good questions with all the necessary information? If these are both valid questions in their current form, we can look at how to make this work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="218" LastActivityDate="2015-07-22T10:15:46.977" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="50" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-27T21:13:34.127" Score="9" ViewCount="556" Body="&lt;p&gt;This site will enter public beta soon, which means it's time to give a few users moderator privileges. Ideally, moderators are elected by the community, but until this site reaches a critical mass to hold an election, we will be appointing some provisional moderators to fill that role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We need your help. Please nominate some folks you might like to see become the provisional moderators for this site. Your input will provide some valuable support to help us make our selections. You can read more about the process here: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/07/moderator-pro-tempore/&quot;&gt;Moderators Pro Tempore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Nomination Process:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nominate a user by adding an 'answer' below. Each nomination should be a separate answer. Link the name to the user’s profile (parent and meta) so we can see their activity. I added a short template (below) to help you with that process. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self nominations are encouraged.&lt;/strong&gt; This is a volunteer activity, so users should not feel obligated to accept these positions. A self nomination is simply a way to say, &quot;I am very much interested in this, so let my record speak for itself.&quot; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nominations can include links to other activities: Area 51 participation, participation in other sites, or any relevant thoughts/links that may help us make an informed decision. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The nominee should indicate their acceptance&lt;/strong&gt; by editing the answer (not commenting) to say they accept. Optionally, nominees are encouraged to write a bit about themselves following the nomination. You can use the &lt;code&gt;---&lt;/code&gt; markup to separate the nominee's commentary from the original nomination. See the example below.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Here is what we'll be looking for in a moderator candidate:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are seeking out members who are deeply engaged in the community's development; members who:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Have been consistently active during the earliest weeks of this site's creation. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Show an interest in their meta's community-building activities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lead by example, showing patience and respect for their fellow community members in everything they write.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Exhibit those intangible traits discussed in &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2009/05/a-theory-of-moderation/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Theory of Moderation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an example nomination entry. You can copy-and-paste from the format below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;[username](&amp;lt;main profile link&amp;gt;) &amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;[Meta Profile](&amp;lt;meta profile link&amp;gt;) &amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Notes:&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;why you feel nominee would be a useful addition to the pro tem choices&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;---&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;(this section is edited in by the nominee)&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;I accept/decline this nomination&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;I am name/age/location/fun fact/all optional. I live in location, so I am generally active on this site from &amp;lt;time&amp;gt; to &amp;lt;time&amp;gt;. Some other things you may want to know about me are&lt;/code&gt;&amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;etc.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="45" LastActivityDate="2015-08-04T08:53:45.190" Title="Who should moderate this site?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="11" FavoriteCount="2"/>
  <row Id="51" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="52" CreationDate="2015-07-28T15:17:04.473" Score="3" ViewCount="50" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a question about an Arabic word – specifically, how to appropriately morph the word to make it diminutive – because I wish to use the word and its morphed (diminutive) form in an English writing project. I do not know any Arabic, and while I have attempted to research this topic, my knowledge of Arabic is too limited to feel confident that I have correctly understood what I have found.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It may be that it is not appropriate to ask such a question here; I know during the 51 phase there was a question regarding questions in English and a desire at least among some users to keep them limited to truly sincere students of the language – and sadly, I do not have the time to be that. The answers to this question suggested to me that this site is really primarily for people who already speak Arabic, not for teaching English speakers (that is, that the site is the Arabic analogue of the English Language &amp;amp; Usage site, &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the English Language Learners site).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, the existing &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/q/8/275&quot;&gt;meta question&lt;/a&gt; on the subject does suggest that it is open to all levels, the analogue of ELL as well as EL&amp;amp;U. I assume that this more-recent discussion is more reflective of the community that is actually here, but I wish to be sure. Moreover, it may be that my question is too basic to even qualify me as a “beginning student,” as indeed, I am not studying the language as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wish to respect this community, and if my question is not appropriate, I will not ask it. It is important for new Stack Exchange sites to set boundaries on what is on-topic, and to try to avoid setting precedents that will cause trouble in the future. I will simply move forward with what I have found and hope it’s close enough so that Arabic speakers who read my work can appreciate what I was going for (since the work is in English, context will be sufficient to understand the distinction for those who understand no Arabic; I merely would like for Arabic speakers to see it as “right.”)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="275" LastActivityDate="2015-07-28T16:55:19.313" Title="On-topic to ask about Arabic, as someone who neither knows nor is studying the language?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;asking-questions&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="52" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="51" CreationDate="2015-07-28T16:55:19.313" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;The website is not only for already-speaking Arabic. It's open to all levels, as all other Stack-exchange websites. You can ask the most basic question you have (Eg. Alphabets). If you misunderstood something, people will correct you. Just try to be clear on your questions: your problem, what you understand and what you didn't understand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The website is just started, on-topic/off-topic is not really defined. We should learn from new questions and define what should be on-topic and what should be off-topic. The more questions we have, the faster we can define the rules. Therefore, I encourage you to ask and ask as long as your questions respect the global guidelines of StackExchange.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-07-28T16:55:19.313" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="53" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2015-07-29T05:01:30.033" Score="10" Body="&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/42&quot;&gt;BigOTHER&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/42&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/42.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/42&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/42.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/1397514&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/flair/1397514.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I definitely nominate &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/42/bigother?tab=profile&quot;&gt;BigOTHER&lt;/a&gt; as he is a very active member in this community &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/42/bigother?tab=answers&quot;&gt;answering&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/42/bigother?tab=activity&amp;amp;sort=comments&quot;&gt;clarifying&lt;/a&gt; and many more (even since the very earliest moments).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Plus, he has a real big knowledge not only in the Arabic Language, but also in the managing and moderating stuff (He only needs some few more reputations to access the moderator tools), with a rich &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/42/bigother&quot;&gt;Arabic-meta profile&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I accept this nomination. Thank you [F. Julian]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am Assem Ch~ / bigOTHER, PhD student in Computer Science. I live in location GMT+1, so I am mainly active on this site from 19:00 GMT to 21:00 GMT. These few months I may appear for few times also along: 9:00 GMT - 17:00 GMT. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a Native Arabic Speaker. My study/work on Natural Language Processing/Information Retrieval/Speech Synthesis pushed me to extend my knowledge on Arabic but still too far from a linguist knowledge. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172" LastEditorUserId="42" LastEditDate="2015-08-01T09:12:22.997" LastActivityDate="2015-08-01T09:12:22.997" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="54" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-29T15:48:02.453" Score="2" ViewCount="75" Body="&lt;p&gt;Prompted by the recent call for &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/q/50/10&quot;&gt;Moderator Pro Tem nominations&lt;/a&gt;, I was wondering how important bilingualism would be in choosing a moderator for this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, communication is an important factor in any healthy moderator team, not only in communicating among themselves, but with the site users as well as with the Stack Exchange team themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should, then, one be fluent in both English &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; Arabic before he be considered as a moderator? Or would it be viable to have moderators who are not particularly fluent in one or the other, so long as there's at least somebody else on the moderator team who &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; (and can thus handle the relevant issues)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2015-07-29T16:08:20.703" Title="How important is it for a site moderator to be bilingual?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;&lt;official-language&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="55" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="54" CreationDate="2015-07-29T16:08:20.703" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since this site is (at least in part) a full-immersion site, I would say it is almost &lt;em&gt;essential&lt;/em&gt; that the candidate be fluent in reading and writing the language being discussed on the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speaking as a Stack Exchange employee who watches over these sites until we can appoint your provisional moderators &amp;mdash; it can be difficult at times to moderate for content when you cannot always understand the nuances of what folks are asking about. I can typically work my way through the subject-agnostic issues to get you through the private beta, but if someone had moderate without knowing the language longer term, I don't think they would be as effective a moderator as they &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="240" LastActivityDate="2015-07-29T16:08:20.703" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="56" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-07-29T21:29:43.743" Score="6" ViewCount="73" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Tajweed (Arabic: تجويد‎ tajwīd, IPA: [tædʒˈwiːd], meaning&#xA;  &quot;elocution&quot;), sometimes rendered as tajwid, refers to the rules&#xA;  governing pronunciation during recitation of the Qur'an.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tajweed mainly is considered as a Quran Science. I am wondering whether we should consider questions about it:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On-topic, and reserve tags for it: &lt;code&gt;Tajweed&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Iqlab&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Idgham&lt;/code&gt;, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Or Off-topic and migrating them to Islam.SE since there are already &lt;a href=&quot;https://islam.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/tajweed&quot;&gt;questions about Tajweed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-08-02T09:02:37.440" Title="Asking about Tajweed rules On-topic or not?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;off-topic&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="58" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="65" CreationDate="2015-08-01T19:34:10.267" Score="2" ViewCount="39" Body="&lt;p&gt;Isn't it more constructive to oblige people who want to down vote an answer or a question to leave a comment explaining their point? Like that the owner can change it to be better .&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2015-08-04T08:26:30.883" Title="Leave a comment when down voting" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;down-votes&gt;&lt;comments&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="59" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2015-08-01T20:27:19.927" Score="2" Body="&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/68&quot;&gt;Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/68&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/68.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/68&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/68.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/367210&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/flair/367210.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suggest &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/68/swift&quot;&gt;Swift&lt;/a&gt; for moderation. He is an active member of the community &lt;a href=&quot;https://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/68/swift?tab=answers&quot;&gt;Answering&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/68/swift?tab=activity&quot;&gt;Clarifying&lt;/a&gt;; And He shows a deep knowledge of Arabic Language and a motivation to push this website forward. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I accept this nomination, Thank you @bigOther.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am Houssem K., I am a Software engineer and  a native speaker of Arabic, I am available between 18:00 GMT and 20:00 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My love for poetry and the Arabic language allowed me to have a good understanding of the language, and I hope to be able to help other advance in their study of the language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I hope to be able to help move this web site to success.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastEditorUserId="68" LastEditDate="2015-08-02T09:58:01.237" LastActivityDate="2015-08-02T09:58:01.237" CommentCount="5" CommunityOwnedDate="2015-08-02T09:24:35.553"/>
  <row Id="60" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2015-08-02T09:00:49.520" Score="0" Body="&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/9/nean-der-thal&quot;&gt;Nean Der Thal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/9/nean-der-thal&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/9.png&quot; width=&quot;208&quot; height=&quot;58&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/9/nean-der-thal&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/9.png&quot; width=&quot;208&quot; height=&quot;58&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/550702&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/flair/550702.png&quot; width=&quot;208&quot; height=&quot;58&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am Mohammed, I am 35 and I work in the aviation safety business. I am an Arabic native speaker, I also speak two other languages. I am active on the internet almost all day (except when I am sleeping, waiting for someone to invent something to keep us connected during that as well).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I live mainly in the Middle East but due to my work I travel all the time. Hence, I am one of the top members in &lt;a href=&quot;http://travel.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;Travel.SE&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have good knowledge about SE rules, I nomintate myself not because I am a native speaker or because of my Arabic language skills, but because I am personally a big fan of the SE concept in general and I would like to be a part in keeping this new SE site in shape when it comes to SE concept as most Arabs (including me before) are familiar with the forums` rules, which is mainly different from SE rules. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastEditorUserId="9" LastEditDate="2015-08-02T20:35:50.447" LastActivityDate="2015-08-02T20:35:50.447" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="61" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="56" CreationDate="2015-08-02T09:02:37.440" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Tajweed is a part of Quran scince in general, and usually is targeted by Islamic schlars rather than Arabic language experts. Hence, I believe it should be off-topic here and I also believe that Islam.SE is the place for Tajweed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastActivityDate="2015-08-02T09:02:37.440" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="62" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2015-08-03T18:40:11.240" Score="5" Body="&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172&quot;&gt;F.Julian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/172.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/flair/172.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suggest &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172&quot;&gt;F.Julian&lt;/a&gt; for moderation. He is an active member of the community &lt;a href=&quot;https://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172?tab=activity&quot;&gt;Clarifying&lt;/a&gt; in the site and in &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172/f-julian?tab=activity&quot;&gt;meta&lt;/a&gt; too, &lt;a href=&quot;https://arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172?tab=answers&quot;&gt;Answering &lt;/a&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/users/172/f-julian?tab=answers&quot;&gt;meta&lt;/a&gt;); He prove the will and skills to moderate. He has good English/Arabic as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you @BigOTHER! I accept this nomination!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am called Fadi and works in the Middle East. I am available almost all the time between 6:00 GMT and 18:00 GMT. I am a native speaker- I actually spent some of my childhood thinking using the Standard Arabic :). Maybe, that's why I am now very strict in grammars and the correct structure!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wish this Arabic site the success as other SE sites have!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastEditorUserId="172" LastEditDate="2015-08-04T08:53:45.190" LastActivityDate="2015-08-04T08:53:45.190" CommentCount="5" CommunityOwnedDate="2015-08-03T18:40:11.240"/>
  <row Id="63" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="64" CreationDate="2015-08-04T05:50:30.523" Score="5" ViewCount="105" Body="&lt;p&gt;I came across &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/q/253/172&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Arabic Language beta site&lt;/a&gt; which asks about some references to learn the Arabic language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is this kind of questions considered as on-topic or off-topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Usually, such questions should be closed as off-topic as the internet is full of learning materials (even if the learner couldn't find some books in libraries). On the other hand, only native speakers know the differences between the materials (and books)as there are many dialects and even wrong Arabic grammars..&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/QdW83.jpg&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/QdW83.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;beta Question&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172" LastEditorUserId="42" LastEditDate="2015-08-04T09:37:24.423" LastActivityDate="2015-08-05T14:32:16.440" Title="Are references questions ontopic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;off-topic&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="64" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="63" CreationDate="2015-08-04T07:25:36.743" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it should be off-topic as it's primarily opinion-based. There is no exact right answer, you will find lot of answers not right/not wrong. Each one will think of a set of books. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In stackoverflow, suggestion of books is off-topic:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Questions asking us to recommend or find a book, tool, software&#xA;  library, tutorial or other off-site resource are off-topic for Stack&#xA;  Overflow as they tend to attract opinionated answers and spam.&#xA;  Instead, describe the problem and what has been done so far to solve&#xA;  it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackoverflow.com/a/255471/1327005&quot;&gt;answer&lt;/a&gt; explaining why it should be off-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-08-04T07:25:36.743" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="65" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="58" CreationDate="2015-08-04T08:26:30.883" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;As BigOTHER &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/58/leave-a-comment-when-down-voting#comment79_58&quot;&gt;commented&lt;/a&gt;, this exact question was already been &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/a/2373/271870&quot;&gt;answered&lt;/a&gt; in this &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/135/encouraging-people-to-explain-downvotes&quot;&gt;main meta question&lt;/a&gt;. So, I'll just re-post the answer again with minor edits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The comments are there for people who want to explain their downvotes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The only thing I can think of is &lt;strong&gt;an AJAX &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; reminder for users when they cast downvotes&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/IUDi1.jpg&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/IUDi1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dowsn votes reminder&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Please consider adding a comment if you think this post can be improved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After the first downvote, we can't say we didn't remind them, and honestly that's as good as it gets. Forcing a comment will end in even worse results.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PS&lt;/strong&gt;: this is implemented and live for users with reputation below 2000. It is shown on every downvote until you get to 2k.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172" LastActivityDate="2015-08-04T08:26:30.883" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="66" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="63" CreationDate="2015-08-05T13:21:52.410" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am the asker of that question and I believe It's on topic. I don't really care about my question, but for the good of this site I believe this kind of question must be encouraged. Here is some details &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it fruitful to search on Google?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The fact that Internet is full of material is a reason way this reference-request question has to be allowed because in general what you get by Google results are poor pedagogic things written by unknown authors with no guarantee of the quality of the exposition and of the material. and the lake of a substantial data base on the Internet of Arabic books makes your request unreachable (sits like goodreads has limited Arabic books titles). I got just a single answer but I don't think I could find the references proposed by searching on Google.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applied Vs theory .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In some way I understand why stackoverflow has baned this kind of question, and In some sense why things is different here, because stackoverflow  is based on an applied science, but SE sites like &lt;a href=&quot;http://cstheory.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/reference-request&quot;&gt;Theoretical Computer Science&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://math.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/reference-request&quot;&gt;Mathematics&lt;/a&gt; as they are based on theoretical science, have always welcomed this questions. Moreover, I still think that the formulation of questions in the link given by BigOTHER are totally different from my asked question ( I didn't ask neither about the best nor about the worst ).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it an opinion based question ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is an opinion based question? is an experience based question an opinion based question? ; In the general meaning of opinion : yes, it is. but I don't think this is the type of the question this attribution is made for. Experience is a justified opinion (in general by objective factors, but the choice of those factors and their importance is an opinion ) and it's no longer a simple opinion, and the central idea of SE is to exchange experience and knowledge. And I think question like &lt;code&gt;what is the best reference on ...&lt;/code&gt; has to be changed to &lt;code&gt;what you have read on ...&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;based on what you have read, what do you recommend on ...&lt;/code&gt; and easily an opinion-based become an experience-based and I believe this is fine for our community. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, if that kind of question turn to a &lt;a href=&quot;http://math.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/big-list&quot;&gt;Big-list&lt;/a&gt; question (I never seen that in Math SE). in its own I don't think it's a problem, but If moderators feel that lazy answers is given I think this kind of question has to be changed to Community Wiki. They can also organize answers in one answer containing what it was proposed so long.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Restriction Vs any other solution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The best place to learn  is the place without lot of restrictions.&#xA;I think in community like ours, restrictions have to be taken as the last possible correction measure. If some kind of questions makes problem of organization, adding new tags will help, and people not interested in some type questions (for example with not single exact answer) don't have to spend time by acceding in these questions, and vice versa. and I believe this flexibility will guarantee the growth of this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="30" LastEditorUserId="30" LastEditDate="2015-08-05T14:32:16.440" LastActivityDate="2015-08-05T14:32:16.440" CommentCount="9"/>
  <row Id="67" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-08-14T10:34:21.800" Score="2" ViewCount="49" Body="&lt;p&gt;We have this question here &lt;a href=&quot;https://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/232/%D9%87%D9%84-%D9%8A%D9%88%D8%AC%D8%AF-%D8%B3%D8%B1-%D8%A8%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%BA%D9%8A-%D9%81%D9%8A-%D8%A7%D8%AE%D8%AA%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%87-%D8%B3%D8%A8%D8%AD%D8%A7%D9%86%D9%87-%D9%83%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AD%D8%B2%D9%86-%D9%81%D9%8A-%D9%87%D8%B0%D9%87-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A2%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA&quot;&gt;هل يوجد سر بلاغي في اختياره سبحانه كلمة الحزن في هذه الآيات؟&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Translation of header: Is there a rhetorical secret in choosing the word Sadness/الحزن in those verses?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OP thought that using that word is strange while it is not. The only strange thing is that it comes always denied or forbidden; And that's not a linguistic issue but a context one. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So shouldn't we brand all questions asked about Quran but the answer is not linguistic as &lt;strong&gt;OFF-TOPIC&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quran is a basic stone in Arabic language so we should expect lot of questions about its verses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-08-14T10:34:21.800" Title="Questions about Quran that can't be answered linguistically, off-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;off-topic&gt;&lt;quran&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="68" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-08-22T16:10:58.603" Score="1" ViewCount="46" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want to ask what a particular word means when translated to English, but I don't want to ask an overly simple question since those types of questions aren't typically very good for SE sites, in my understanding. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I looked it up using Google Translate, but I'm aware that many, if not most, languages have homonyms, and so I don't want to jump to conclusions as Google Translate very often tends to have trouble with homonyms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="400" OwnerDisplayName="SarahofGaia" LastActivityDate="2015-09-03T02:10:58.893" Title="Really basic learner's questions on-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="69" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-08-24T06:41:47.247" Score="1" ViewCount="49" Body="&lt;p&gt;We had the &lt;a href=&quot;https://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/296/dictionary-of-classical-judeo-arabic&quot;&gt;question&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Judeo-Arabic_languages&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Judeo-Arabic&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://ar.wikipedia.org/wiki/%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A%D8%A9_%D9%8A%D9%87%D9%88%D8%AF%D9%8A%D8%A9&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;عربية يهودية&lt;/a&gt; , I never heard of it till now. It's a set of  colloquial Arabic dialects written in Hebrew.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should we consider it as any other colloquial Arabic? or not since it's not written in Arabic letters but Hebrew?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;whether we do or we don't, questions about it in Arabic on-topic or off-topic? and why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also questions about it in Hebrew allowed or not?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-08-25T19:13:28.993" Title="Questions about Judeo-Arabic is it on-topic or off-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;off-topic&gt;&lt;judeo-arabic&gt;&lt;on-topic&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="4"/>
  <row Id="70" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-08-24T12:18:20.643" Score="2" ViewCount="44" Body="&lt;p&gt;how to say تشكيل in english. and are questions about تشكيل on topic?. if so tag tachkil needed??&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="22" LastEditDate="2015-08-25T20:20:00.957" LastActivityDate="2015-08-25T20:20:00.957" Title="how to say تشكيل in english" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1"/>
  <row Id="71" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="70" CreationDate="2015-08-24T18:45:52.533" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;In English, the technical term would be &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arabic_diacritics&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;diacritics&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, but that would also include the إعجام; I don't know that there's a particular (or at least a &lt;em&gt;common&lt;/em&gt;) English term for تشكيل themselves (although the حركات are often just referred to as &quot;vowel marks&quot;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't see why they would be off-topic at all; inre tagging the only question I would worry about is how the tags would be broken up (i.e. should حركات, تشكيل, إعجام be synonyms of each other, or tagged separately?).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At this point, there's no real harm in just creating the tag &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/tashkeel&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;tashkeel&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;tashkeel&lt;/a&gt; (or &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/diacritics&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;diacritics&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;diacritics&lt;/a&gt;) as needed &amp;mdash; you only need 150 reputation to create new tags &amp;mdash; and figuring out whether any synonyming or tag cleanup is actually necessary after people start actually using it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2015-08-24T18:45:52.533" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="72" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="70" CreationDate="2015-08-24T19:27:22.760" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would suggest &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/vowelization&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;vowelization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for tashkeel:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;In Arabic and Hebrew - supplying the vowels (diacritics), normally not&#xA;  written to show the correct pronunciation, used in dictionaries,&#xA;  children's books, religious texts and textbooks for learners. Arabic&#xA;  terms: tashkiil (تشكيل), taHriik (تحريك) - (action of supplying the&#xA;  vowel points) , also known as ḥarakāt&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Surely on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2015-08-24T19:27:22.760" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="73" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="69" CreationDate="2015-08-25T19:13:28.993" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Judaeo-Arabic is Arabic written in Hebrew letters. Many of the mediaeval Judaeo-Arabic texts are written in excellent classical Arabic. For example, there is the famous translation of the Hebrew Bible by Sa'id al-Fayyumi from the 9th century CE. There are many manuscripts of this both in Arabic script and in Hebrew script. So of course Judaeo-Arabic is part of Arabic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="37" LastActivityDate="2015-08-25T19:13:28.993" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="74" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-08-26T08:27:50.910" Score="1" ViewCount="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;We had a question here : &lt;a href=&quot;https://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions/304/why-is-the-word-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%87-formed-as-one-character&quot;&gt;Why is the word لله formed as one character?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The question is a mixture between computing and Arabic language: font shaping, and definitely can't be asked in Stack-overflow or Graphic design because the answer is mostly linguistic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We should define the line when to consider a question like that on-topic and when not. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastEditorUserId="42" LastEditDate="2015-08-26T18:36:21.410" LastActivityDate="2015-08-26T20:04:31.673" Title="Questions about fonts, shaping , on-topic or off-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;off-topic&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="75" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="74" CreationDate="2015-08-26T18:22:40.583" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;The linked question's answer was completely specific to the Arabic Language domain, and it is unlikely an answer coming from a graphical design point of view would have provided the necessary information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With respect to the line between on-topic and off-topic questions, if the question can be answered without any significant knowledge of the Arabic language, then the question may be considered off-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="412" LastEditorUserId="412" LastEditDate="2015-08-26T20:04:31.673" LastActivityDate="2015-08-26T20:04:31.673" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="76" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-09-01T15:52:54.890" Score="13" ViewCount="167" Body="&lt;p&gt;We're still in the process of assembling the &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/q/50/45&quot;&gt;pro tem moderator team&lt;/a&gt; for this site. It's been a little hard to get a team together, mainly due to lack of response and activity surrounding the meta thread - and the site itself. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So as far as the moderator thread goes: Even if you don't want to nominate yourself or anyone else, please vote on answers there so we have a little more information to go on about the community's approval of each candidate. While this isn't an &lt;em&gt;election&lt;/em&gt; - the Community Team selects pro tem moderators for beta sites - it's best to be able to make these selections with more input from members of the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But outside of the question of pro tem moderators, general activity on Arabic SE is worryingly low. The site has &lt;a href=&quot;http://arabic.stackexchange.com/questions&quot;&gt;103 questions&lt;/a&gt; at time of this writing. I have to be honest: we've shut down sites after just 14 days of private beta that had more questions than Arabic does after &lt;strong&gt;48 days&lt;/strong&gt;. Arabic was allowed to survive past private beta because it's a language site. We've got &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/categories/3/culture?tab=beta&quot;&gt;tons of those on the network&lt;/a&gt;, and they're frequently a little lower in activity than other sites - but we know that the model is straightforward to set up, and useful even at low volume. But this is the lowest volume we've seen yet... and that's got me worried. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'd like to direct you to this recent post about &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/257614/165581&quot;&gt;when we graduate sites, and when we shut them down&lt;/a&gt;. Specifically:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;What does this mean? &lt;strong&gt;If there's enough moderation for a public beta site to consistently remain free of spam, for flags to be cleared, and for our Be Nice policy to be upheld, your site will remain open.&lt;/strong&gt; However, if community leaders drop off, flags sit without being addressed, and we can’t find any suitable volunteers to step forward, the site gets closed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm not seeing the leadership coalescing in this community that a Stack Exchange site really needs to thrive - or even just survive. I don't just mean moderators; I'm talking about the core community of active users who lead the site through their activity on the main Q&amp;amp;A site and their participation on meta.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sites don't often come back from problems like this one. Momentum is extremely hard to build once it's lost, and Arabic SE didn't have much momentum to begin with. I hope this community can rally, but that will mean a lot more activity from everyone involved - in addition to more users joining the conversation about pro-tem mods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="45" LastEditorUserId="45" LastEditDate="2015-09-08T19:21:19.750" LastActivityDate="2015-09-08T19:21:19.750" Title="Moderation, and the outlook for this site" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;&lt;site-health&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1"/>
  <row Id="77" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="68" CreationDate="2015-09-03T02:10:58.893" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you want to make sure your terms are translated correctly, Wikipedia is sometimes your best bet. If you want to know &quot;Lord of the Rings&quot; in Arabic, don't put that into Google Translate unless you want to be laughed at. Instead, find the page in English and switch to العربية&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="440" LastActivityDate="2015-09-03T02:10:58.893" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="78" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="76" CreationDate="2015-09-03T02:19:22.610" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Moderation may be difficult if the user base is segmented between English speakers with very little Arabic, and Arabic speakers with very little English. I would be willing to perform moderation duties, although I am new to this SE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="440" LastActivityDate="2015-09-03T02:19:22.610" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="79" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-09-03T02:25:09.587" Score="0" ViewCount="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think Arabic is always unreasonably hard to read in most programs. What are some solutions to make the Arabic font more readable?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="440" LastActivityDate="2015-09-03T02:25:09.587" Title="What are appropriate norms for formatting?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;formatting&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2"/>
  <row Id="80" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="79" CreationDate="2015-09-03T02:25:09.587" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have some suggestions:&#xA;1) always have &lt;strong&gt;العربية&lt;/strong&gt; in bold.&#xA;2) use the heading ## Header 2 ##&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="440" LastActivityDate="2015-09-03T02:25:09.587" CommentCount="0"/>
  <row Id="81" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-09-08T17:57:13.463" Score="10" ViewCount="195" Body="&lt;p&gt;Last week, I wrote a bit of &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.arabic.stackexchange.com/q/76/45&quot;&gt;an S.O.S. call for Arabic SE&lt;/a&gt;. The call was for us to figure out a way to bail out this site, which is sinking slowly due to inactivity. I cited specifically the difficulty we're finding in putting together a moderator staff and the extremely low question volume Arabic has had since launch. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few brave souls responded to the call. There was a blip on the radar for the pro-tem moderator hunt, and a small group of people bumped our question count by 12 this past week. (We now have 115 questions at time of writing - but that number is still lower than the threshold below which most sites won't make it out of private beta.) &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the site had been getting 12 questions per week consistently since the private beta, I would consider that a low but respectable amount of activity - but I must assume even this level of activity wouldn't continue if the site were to remain open. This is a handful of people trying to bail out the site, when what we need is a crew working together to build momentum. Without that cohesive community, we have to abandon ship. &lt;strong&gt;We'll be shutting down this site on Monday, September 14.&lt;/strong&gt; There will be an archive of all posts available &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/62022/arabic-language&quot;&gt;on Area 51&lt;/a&gt; shortly after closure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'd really like to see this topic rebooted in a new Area 51 proposal. This one got a lot of support in Area 51 and launched relatively quickly, but somehow the promising community evaporated when private beta rolled around: only 1.8% of committers fulfilled their commitment. If you can build a community that will pull together for the next private beta, the Arabic Language topic could enjoy the same success here as many of the other language sites we host.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="45" LastActivityDate="2015-09-14T12:46:52.053" Title="Arabic Language will be closing on Monday, September 14" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;featured&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="6"/>
  <row Id="82" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="81" CreationDate="2015-09-14T12:46:52.053" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is an excellent Arabic site at &quot;Wordreference&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For questions in European languages: &lt;a href=&quot;http://forum.wordreference.com/forums/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A%D8%A9-arabic.41/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://forum.wordreference.com/forums/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A%D8%A9-arabic.41/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For questions in Arabic this one: &lt;a href=&quot;http://forum.wordreference.com/forums/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D9%81%D9%82%D8%B7.47/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://forum.wordreference.com/forums/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D9%81%D9%82%D8%B7.47/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has excellent well-informed moderators.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="37" LastActivityDate="2015-09-14T12:46:52.053" CommentCount="0"/>
</posts>